Victoria Arowosafe

FREDERICTON, NB | 506-998-1841 | oluwabusayo.arowosafe@gmail.com

Objective

Recently graduated as a full stack developer with proficiency in programming languages and software
development. Enthusiastic and self-motivated Master of Business Administration graduate with five
years of experience in administration. Seeking an entry-level position as a full stack developer to launch
into the programming industry.

Education

CERTIFICATE | APRIL 2023 | UNIVERSITY OF NEW BRUNSWICK

• Full Stack Development

MBA | DECEMBER 2019 | WESTCLIFF UNIVERSITY

• MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

B.SC| APRIL 2014 | UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN

MICROBIOLOGY

Skills & Abilities

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML
 CSS
 JAVASCRIPT
 REST APIS

J. QUERY
 REACT.JS
 NODE.JS
 JSON

DATABASES

• SQL

MONGODB

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

PROJECT MANAGEMENT
 TRELLO
 JIRA

BUSINESS ANALYSIS
 SCRUM

SOFT SKILLS

PROBLEM-SOLVING • DATA ANALYSIS

EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION • TEAMWORK

LEADERSHIP
 ORGANISATION

Experience

HEALTHCARE ADMINISTRATOR | SERENITY MEDICAL CORP. | FEBRUARY 2022 – TILL DATE Fredericton. NB.

- Analyze data and managing data system to ensure the accuracy of patients' details, medical history, reports, requisitions, and treatment plans.
- Perform administrative and clerical duties such as sending faxes, emails, receiving phone enquiries, tracking budgets, and reconciling financial records.
- Process confidential patient information and requests while ensuring compliance with HIPAA privacy and security regulations.

BUSINESS ANALYSIS (INTERN) | TECHSOL CORPORATION | FEBRUARY 2020 – NOVEMBER 2020 Princeton, New Jersey.

- Develop standard software documents including Discovery, SOW, business requirements, Functional Specifications, Configuration Documents, Use Cases.
- Perform business analysis and complied with regulations, bargaining agreements, and or business processes that relate to a business domain.
- Achievement: Gained valuable knowledge about developing user cases, facilitating meetings, eliciting requirements, project implementation and testing; the use of standard techniques JAD, (Joint Application Development) interviewing, use case modeling, gap-fit analysis, process definition, requirements gathering and management.

ASSISTANT PROJECT COORDINATOR | 9MOBILE TELECOM | MAY 2016 - NOVEMBER 2017 Lagos, Nigeria.

- Direct team on business requirements and tracked progress to ensure project milestones were completed within project constraints.
- Mitigate risk factors through high-level and detailed analysis and remove impediments that can hinder the project team from performing optimally.
- Perform project tracking through concise reports and updates on project management plans, project documents and management reports.
- **Achievement**: Supported the project management team in the upgrading of "TABS" software used daily by hundreds of customer service agents to resolve client issues and enquiries. The upgraded software is more user friendly, has more functions and tested to be more efficient than the old version.